WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN)
Right here right now (burn)
kewashii shura no michi no naka
down a difficult road filled with endless struggles
hito no chizu wo hirogete doko e yuku
where do you think you are going following someone else's map?
gokusaishoku no karasu ga sore wo ubaitotte yaburisuteta
an insightful crow comes along to tear up the map
saa kokoro no me mihiraite shika to ima wo mikiwamero (YEAH)
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth (yeah)
ushinau mono nante nai sa iza mairou
there's nothing to lose, so let's go
WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh! just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase Like a dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE BANG
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire, bang!
Lord Third,
Farewell Forever...!!
Sarutobi...
At the very least this sword...
It was a fitting end for somebody like you
who has mastered
the Shinobi Way.
It feels like my arms are burning...
Orochimaru-sama!
This is where we call off our plan.
Release the Barrier.
We'll head back.
— Yes!
— Release!
The Barrier...!
It's released!
Where is Hokage-sama?
Let's go!
We won't let you get away!
Ninja Art: Spider Web Net!
An adhesive type of string
filled with Chakra...?
Kakashi! They're on the move!
Do we go after them?
No, wait, Guy.
That's right...
If you make a move without
any data on the situation up there,
you will get caught in
the enemy's trap.
I'm totally aware of that.
But regardless of whether
there is a trap or not,
we can't let the enemy get away
at a time like this!
That is the way of the Leaf Shinobi!
So... are you just going to watch?
Kabuto?
So you did know, after all.
So... what are we going to do?
It's about time that
we made a retreat.
You're going to run away
from me again?
Right now...
if we show our cards,
they're most likely going to be copied.
Then again,
it doesn't seem like you've completely
mastered that eye like the Uchiha clan.
Well then...
Temari...
Kankuro!
I'm leaving Sakura with you.
H-Hey!
Why is... this guy so strong?
My existence will not disappear...
I will not disappear!
I cannot disappear!
I told you not to talk to that guy!
Let's go.
Oh, there! That's him...
Go away!
Monster! Monster! Monster...!
You monster! Die!
That's him... Don't get involved, fool!
Don't look at him!
Go away!
To them, I'm just a relic of the past
who they want to see disappear.
So what did I have in this life,
why did I keep living?
And that time, I thought of myself that I...
no, that is what I had to think.
And then knew that
it was the most painful thing.
That I... that my existence didn't matter
to anyone else in the world.
D-Don't come any closer!
The pain of... being all alone...
really is unbearable, isn't it?
The way you feel...
I don't know why,
but I completely understand that it hurts.
But I've met people who are
very important to me now.
I won't allow those important people...
to get hurt!
If not, I will stop you even if
that means... that I have to kill you!
Why...?
How is it that you can fight so much
for other people?
They saved me from the hell
of being all alone.
They accepted me for who I was.
That's why... they are important to me!
Love is a heart that desires to serve
a precious person who is close to oneself,
to love and watch over that person...
Love...
That is why he is so strong?
That's enough, Naruto...
Sakura is okay.
This guy's Chakra must
have been depleted as well...
Sakura's sand crumbled
a long time ago.
Oh, I see...
I've had enough... Stop here.
Gaara?
I've never seen Gaara in such
a weakened state before...
All right.
Uzumaki Naruto, huh?
One of these days, even I...
"LOVE"
Temari... Kankuro...
— Huh?
Sorry...
D-Don't worry about it...
Rain...
The sky has started to weep as well...
We will begin the memorial service
for the Third Hokage,
who lost his life in this battle,
as well as the other victims
of this battle.
It's started...
In the end,
all we could do was just watch...
Why?
Why did Old Man Hokage have to die?
Why...?
It's already been a year...
It's not easy to laugh
hiding your sadness.
I heard from your teacher that
you're the center of laughter...
I'm not sad at all!
It's a very honorable thing for
a Shinobi to die doing their duty!
My dad and mom sacrificed their lives
to protect this village
from the Demon Fox...
They're heroes!
I am the child of the heroes!
I'm not sad to be alone.
And besides, these are tears of joy.
It's all right.
I know that you're curled up
holding your knees by yourself.
But you're not alone...
Huh?
The Shinobi of the Hidden Leaf Village
have the will of fire...
Will of fire...?
It's the strong will to protect
the Leaf Village.
As long as they have this will of fire,
everybody in this village are all family.
Iruka... I wonder if you have it?
Yeah...
For Hayate...?
The Third Hokage's funeral
has already started. Make it quick.
You too, Kakashi-Senpai, is it for Obito-san...?
If you're always thinking of
an excuse for your tardiness,
you should just come earlier.
I do... from early in the morning.
It's just that,
whenever I come here
I just want to punish myself
for being such a fool in the past.
Humph...
Shinobi, no matter what kind
of situation they are in,
cannot show their emotion.
You must always prioritize your mission,
and never shed a tear in
any kind of situation...
Iruka-sensei...
Hmm?
Why do people risk their own lives
for other people?
When one person dies...
their past, their present life,
and their future disappear along with them.
Many people die doing their duty
and fighting in battle...
And shockingly easily, too.
Hayate was one of them.
Those who pass away also
have dreams and ambitions.
But everyone has something else,
just as important.
Parents, siblings, friends, lovers...
Those who are dear to them.
They trust each other and help each other,
the people whom they've cherished
since the day they were born.
And that string which connects
those people
becomes stronger and
thicker as time goes by...
It can't be explained by logic...
Those who hold those strings just do it,
because it's important to them.
Yeah, I kind of get it.
But...
It's tough to die.
It's not like he just died for nothing.
He left us something very important.
Well, you'll eventually understand
one of these days.
Yeah, I kind of get that too!
The rain's stopped.
Bye! Iruka-sensei!
Yeah...
Third Hokage-sama,
the will of fire you spoke of
seems to have been passed on
to the young Leaves.
The flame in their hearts
which you lit
will burn bright and strong...
And it will shine upon this village,
and watch over and protect us.
It will become a new Hokage...
one of these days...
They did manage to avoid annihilation,
but it seems the damage
is pretty extensive.
The village that was once
at the height of its glory...
How sad...
How unlike you.
You have lingering affections
for your old home?
Even you?
No, not at all.
gaman no renzoku dattaro
a cycle of hardship, right?
kokoro de naiteita ndarou
inside, we were crying, right?
jibun de kimeta sono yume dake wa yuzurenai ndarou
but the one thing we won't give up is the dream we've chosen, right?
wakiyaku dakedo
it's a secondary role
kage no hito dakedo
a role in the shadows
yume to mukiau toki kurai
but in reaching for that dream
man naka ni isasete shoujiki ni isasete
let us stay centered, let us stay true
ima made nandomo nan toka akiramezu ni
over and over, we hung on without giving up
ima made nandomo tachi agatte kita janai ka
over and over, we kept coming back up
ima made nandomo
over and over, we believed and dreamed
bokura
nandomo
shinjite
yume mite nandomo
ima made nandomo baka o mite kita janai ka
over and over, we've seen fools
ima made nandomo hito no kage ni tatte kita janai ka
over and over, we've stood in the shadows of others
saa shuyaku da yo jibun no yume kurai wagamama de isasete
now, it's our turn... let us bask in our dreams
The ritual ends, and morning mist
will be covering all soon.
Silence...
In that white mist,
the shadow quietly sharpens its fangs.
It awakens childhood memory,
disappointment, ire, and resolve.
The cog wheel named destiny
slowly begins to turn...
Next time:
"Return of the Morning Mist."